Inventory of the Citizens for Reagan Records
Hoover Institution Archives
Citizens for Reagan Records
1975-1986
81141
Hoover Institution Archives
109 manuscript boxes, 2 cubic foot boxes, 9 oversize boxes, 605 video tapes, 12 phonodisks, 8 phonotapes (112 linear feet)
The collection relates to the campaign of Ronald Reagan for the Republican Party presidential nomination in 1976. Materials include correspondence, position papers, press releases, memoranda, public opinion polling data, financial records, sound recordings, and video tapes. Includes a few post-1976 records of Citizens for the Republic, the successor organization to Citizens for Reagan.
Citizens for Reagan.
Access
Boxes 2-3 and 110-111 are closed. The remainder of the cllection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1981.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Materials
Richard Wirthlin papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Peter Hannaford papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Ronald Reagan subject collection, Hoover Institution Archives
Lyn Nofziger papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Edwin Meese papers, Hoover Institution Archives
To see a complete listing of all the related collections, please go to Hoover Institution Archives catalog web site at http://library.stanford.edu/webcat and enter the search term Reagan, Ronald
Historical Note
The Citizens for Reagan organization originated from a strong belief of some of his supporters that Ronald Reagan should be persuaded to run for the Republican nomination for president in 1976, becoming Reagan's official campaign committee for the 1976 election. A committee was formed for that purpose with Senator Paul Laxalt, former governor of Nevada, as its chairman. The goal of this committee was to set up an organization to lead an effective political campaign and raise money needed to conduct a successful campaign in the event of the announcement of Ronald Reagan's candidacy for the president of the United States.
In addition to Paul Laxalt, other prominent members of the Republican Party decided to signify their support of Ronald Reagan's candidacy. John P. Sears, a Washington attorney, was chosen to serve as the executive vice-chairman. Other office holders included Jack Courtimanche of Los Angeles to be in charge of financial operations; Loren Smith as legal counsel; Jeffrey Bell as head of research; Henry M. Buchanan as treasurer; and David Keene as the southern states coordinator. Other prominent members were former governor of Kentucky Louis B. Nunn; former California Republican National Committeewoman Mrs. Stanlope C. Ring; retired congressman H. R. Gross of Iowa; and Nebraska insurance executive George Cook. Jim Lake, David Keene, and Lyn Nofziger represented political staff.
Citizens for Reagan had a centralized administrative structure with state offices. All handbills, rally notices and other materials included a notation such as "paid for by the CFR." Each local unit had a chairman and a treasurer at all times, possibly a bookkeeper as well. All local contributions to Citizens for Reagan or to the local subdivision were sent to Washington, D.C. to be deposited. The Washington office also authorized all expenditures.
All activities were carried out on a state-by-state basis using a detailed list of state-level coordinators, members, and addresses. Although the 1976 presidential election results did not fulfill Ronald Reagan's political ambition, the operating procedures and organizational structure used in the Citizens for Reagan operations of 1975-1976, the organizational experience successfully supported his later political ambitions.
Scope and Content of Collection
Citizens for Reagan records are a document the process leading up to Ronald Reagan's bid for the Republican Party presidential nomination in 1976, which he lost to Gerald Ford at the convention. The materials include correspondence, position papers, press releases, memoranda, public opinion polling data, financial records, sound recordings, and video tapes. They reveal elaborate planning, organization, publicity, preparation, and advertisement required to launch a political campaign. The papers are arranged in their original order, with the original folder titles and organizational system devised by the Citizens for Reagan office staff.
Citizens for the Republic.; Reagan, Ronald.; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); Phonotapes.; Presidents--United States--Election--1976.; Video tapes.
- Abortion, 1975 (Folder 1: 1)
- Accounting records, 1975 (Folder 1: 2)
- Accounts payable, New Hampshire, 1975-1976 (Folder 1: 3)
- Accounts receivable, 1976 (Folder 1: 4)
- Advance procedures, 1976 (Folder 1: 5)
- Alphabetical run by state, 1976 (Folder 1: 6)
- Announcement letter, 1975 and undated (Folder 1: 7)
- Announcement of candidacy drafts, 1975 (Folder 1: 8-9)
- Announcement planning, undated (Folder 1: 10)
- Announcement trip, 1975 (Folder 1: 11)
- Ball and McDaniel account, 1976 (Folder 1: 12-14)
- Closed - Contributions and letters after March 31, 1976 (Folder 2: 1)
- Closed - Campaign contribution lists, 1975-1976 (Folder 2: 2-7)
- Closed - Campaign contribution lists, 1975-1976 (Folder 3: 1-6)
- Ball and McDaniel account, 1976 (Folder 4: 1-2)
- Boyd, W. W. correspondence, 1957-1976 (Folder 4: 3)
- Marc W. Ball, 1976 (Folder 4: 4)
- Bell memoranda to Ronald Reagan regarding Gerald R. Ford's selection as Vice-President, 1974 (Folder 4: 5)
- Campaign literature prices, 1975 and undated (Folder 4: 6)
- Campaign materials, 1975 and undated (Folder 4: 6)
- Campaign by state (Folder 4)
  - Florida, 1975 (Folder 4: 8)
  - New York, 1975 (Folder 4: 9)
  - North Carolina, 1975 (Folder 4: 10)
  - North Dakota, 1975 (Folder 4: 11)
  - Ohio, 1975 and undated (Folder 5: 1)
  - Oklahoma, 1975-1976 (Folder 5: 2)
  - Oregon, 1974-1975 (Folder 5: 3)
  - Pennsylvania, 1975 and undated (Folder 5: 4)
  - Rhode Island, 1974-1975 (Folder 5: 5)
  - South Carolina, 1975 (Folder 5: 6)
  - South Dakota, 1975 (Folder 5: 7)
  - Tennessee, 1975 (Folder 5: 8)
  - Texas, 1975 (Folder 5: 9)
  - Utah, undated (Folder 5: 10)
  - Vermont, 1975 (Folder 5: 11)
  - Virginia, 1975-1976 and undated (Folder 5: 12)
  - Washington, 1975 (Folder 5: 13)
  - West Virginia, 1975 (Folder 5: 14)
  - Wisconsin, 1975 (Folder 5: 15)
  - Wyoming, undated (Folder 5: 16)
  - District of Columbia, 1975 (Folder 5: 17)
  - Puerto Rico, undated (Folder 5: 18)
  - Virgin Islands, undated (Folder 5: 19)
  - Guam, undated (Folder 5: 20)
- Canvas script, 1975 and undated (Folder 5: 21)
- Ronald Reagan's current position in caucus states, undated (Folder 5: 22)
- Centrex lists, 1976 (Folder 5: 23)
- China, undated (Folder 5: 24)
- Collateral materials (Folder 5)
  - Headquarters, undated (Folder 5: 25)
  - Other, by state, 1976 and undated (Folder 5: 26)
    - Alabama, 1976 (Folder 6: 1)
    - Alaska, 1976 (Folder 6: 2)
    - Arizona, 1976 and undated (Folder 6: 3)
    - Arkansas, 1976 (Folder 6: 4)
    - California, 1976 (Folder 6: 5)
    - Colorado, undated (Folder 6: 6)
    - Florida, undated (Folder 6: 7)
    - Georgia, 1976 (Folder 6: 8)
    - Idaho, 1976 (Folder 6: 9)
    - Illinois, 1976 (Folder 6: 10)
    - Indiana, undated (Folder 6: 11)
    - Iowa, 1976 (Folder 6: 12)
    - Kansas, 1976 (Folder 6: 13)
    - Kentucky, 1976 (Folder 6: 14)
    - Louisiana, undated (Folder 6: 15)
    - Maryland, 1976 (Folder 6: 16)
    - Massachusetts, 1976 (Folder 6: 17)
    - Michigan, 1976 (Folder 6: 18)
    - Minnesota, 1976 (Folder 6: 19)
    - Mississippi, undated (Folder 6: 20)
    - Missouri, 1976 (Folder 6: 21)
    - Montana, 1976 (Folder 6: 22)
    - Nebraska, 1976 (Folder 6: 23)
    - Nevada, 1976 (Folder 6: 24)
    - New Hampshire, 1976 (Folder 6: 25)
    - New Mexico, 1976 (Folder 6: 26)
    - North Carolina, 1976 (Folder 6: 27)
    - North Dakota, 1976 (Folder 6: 28)
    - Ohio, 1976 (Folder 6: 29)
    - Oklahoma, 1975-1976 (Folder 6: 30)
    - Oregon, 1976 (Folder 6: 31)
    - Rhode Island, 1976 (Folder 6: 32)
    - South Carolina, 1976 (Folder 6: 33)
    - South Dakota, 1976 (Folder 6: 34)
    - Tennessee, undated (Folder 6: 35)
    - Texas, 1975-1976 (Folder 6: 36)
    - Utah, 1976 (Folder 6: 37)
    - Virginia, 1976 (Folder 6: 38)
    - West Virginia, 1976 (Folder 6: 39)
    - Washington, 1976 (Folder 6: 40)
    - Wisconsin, 1976 (Folder 6: 41)
    - Wyoming, undated (Folder 6: 42)
- Common Cause, 1976 (Folder 6: 43-44)
- Congressional Quarterly Weekly Report, 1976 (Folder 6: 45)
- Conservative Political Action Conference, undated (Folder 6: 46)
- Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975 January-June (Folder 7: 1)
  - File copies, 1976 May-November (Folder 7: 2)
  - Incoming, no responses, 1975 February - 1976 July and undated (Folder 7: 3)
  - Incoming, no responses, 1974 December - 1976 June (Folder 7: 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976 May-September (Folder 7: 5-6)
  - Received at Convention, 1976 August (Folder 7: 7)
  - Miscellaneous - Staff, 1975 September - 1976 April (Folder 7: 8)
  - Post-convention, 1976 July-October (Folder 7: 9)
  - By state (Folder 7)
    - Michigan, 1975 March - 1976 August (Folder 7: 10)
    - Michigan, 1974 December - 1975 December (Folder 8: 1-2)
    - New Jersey, 1975 December - 1976 March (Folder 8: 3-5)
    - Virginia, 1975 March - 1976 February (Folder 8: 6-7)
- "The Democratic Presidential Watch", Report prepared by the Republican National Committee, 1976 (Folder 9: 1)
- Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 1976 (Folder 9: 2)
- Energy conservation, 1975 (Folder 9: 3)
- Federal Election Commission brochure, 1976 (Folder 9: 4)
- Financial statements, 1976 (Folder 9: 5)
- Federal Election Law, 1975 (Folder 9: 6)
- Formation of the Citizens for Reagan (CFR) announcment, 1975 (Folder 9: 7)
- General, 1976 (Folder 9: 8)
- Gingold, Julian, undated (Folder 9: 9)
- Ethnic groups, 1975 (Folder 9: 10)
- Goldwater, Barry, 1975-1976 (Folder 9: 11)
- Goldwater, Barry - Letter announcing support for Gerald R. Ford, 1976 (Folder 9: 12)
- Gun control, 1975 (Folder 9: 13)
- Hannaford, Peter briefing, undated (Folder 9: 14)
- Hotel accommodations, 1975 (Folder 9: 15)
- Intercontinental supply, 1976 and undated (Folder 9: 16)
- Informational materials, 1976 and undated (Folder 9: 17)
- Interview, 1975 (Folder 9: 18)
- Florida campaign, 1975 (Folder 9: 19)
- Individual responses to issues (letters about miscellaneous subjects), 1975-1976 (Folder 9: 20)
- Ronald Reagan's taxes in California, 1975 (Folder 9: 21)
- Leaflets and pamphlets, undated (Folder 9: 22)
- Keene, Dave - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Folder 9: 23)
- Legal, 1975 (Folder 9: 24)
- Smith, Loren - Legal counsel, 1976 (Folder 9: 25)
- Letters to Paul Laxalt regarding chairmanship of Citizens for Reagan, 1975 (Folder 9: 26)
- Laxalt correspondence - Post convention, 1976 (Folder 9: 27)
- Letter to Paul Laxalt regarding formation of the Citizens for Reagan, 1975 (Folder 9: 28)
- Letter to Ronald Reagan regarding 1976 July 6 speech (Folder 9: 29)
- McCormick, Ellen - Endorsement of Ronald Reagan, 1976 (Folder 10: 1)
- Mailing list, 1975 (Folder 10: 2)
- Meet the Press transcripts, Hamilton Jordan and Robert S. Strauss as guests, 1976 (Folder 10: 3)
- Memoranda, 1975-1976 (Folder 10: 4)
- National Broadcasting Corporation (NBC) poll, 1975` (Folder 10: 5)
- Military (re computation retired pay), 1975 (Folder 10: 6)
- "Reasons for Reagan" Brochures and negatives, 1976 (Folder 10: 7)
- Mid-western states regional and state chairmen meeting, Kansas City, Missouri, 1976 February 28-29 (Folder 10: 8)
- National Federation Republican Women's Convention, Dallas, Texas, 1975 (Folder 10: 9)
- New Jersey, 1976 (Folder 10: 10)
- New Hampshire, 1975-1976 (Folder 10: 11)
- Newsletter, 1976 (Folder 10: 12)
- North Carolina, 1976 (Folder 10: 13)
- Citizens for Reagan organizational instructions, 1975-1976 (Folder 10: 14)
- Nofziger, Lyn, 1975 (Folder 10: 15)
- Nofziger, Lyn correspondence regarding right to work, 1975 (Folder 10: 16)
- Response to $90 billion plan, 1975 and undated (Folder 10: 17)
- Photocopy of Ronald Reagan's photograph and letter, undated (Folder 10: 18)
- Picture of Ronald Reagan, photocopy, 1975-1976 (Folder 10: 19)
- Peden, Neal, 1975 (Folder 10: 20)
- Personnel data - Citizens for Reagan (CFR), Washington, D.C., 1976 (Folder 10: 21)
- Ronald Reagan's 1976 March 31 speech and Citizens for Reagan's responses to foreign policy charges (Folder 11: 1)
- Ronald Reagan's remarks regarding Gerald Ford/Richard Nixon connection and Lyn Nofziger response to press questions, undated (Folder 11: 2)
- Polls, 1975 (Folder 11: 3)
- Press billings, 1976 (Folder 11: 4)
- Press list, undated (Folder 11: 5)
- Press releases, 1975 (Folder 11: 6)
- Printing, 1976 (Folder 11: 7)
- Publications on Ronald Reagan, 1976 and undated (Folder 11: 8)
- Rarick letters, 1975 (Folder 11: 9)
- Ronald Reagan - Administration accomplishments, 1975-1976 (Folder 11: 10)
- Regional chairmen, undated (Folder 11: 11)
- Regional coordinators, undated (Folder 11: 12)
- Resumes, 1975-1976 and undated (Folder 12: 1-7)
- Right-To-Work, 1975-1976 (Folder 13: 1)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A. (J. St. John television interview with Ronald Reagan on and analysis on NAR), 1974 and undated (Folder 13: 2)
- Rockefeller, Nelson ruling and miscellaneous notes, 1975 and undated (Folder 13: 3)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1975. Letters (Folder 13: 4)
- Running mate choice, 1975 (Folder 13: 5)
- Rusher, William A.'s letter regarding Third Party Commission, 1975 (Folder 13: 6)
- Schedule (Folder 13)
  - 1976 January 8-February 25 (Folder 13: 7)
  - 1976 February 26-March 19 (Folder 13: 8)
  - 1976 March 17-August 7 (Folder 13: 9)
  - 1976 May 18-August 7 (Folder 13: 10)
  - Requests, 1975 December 31 - 1976 January 13 (Folder 13: 11)
- Security, 1976 (Folder 13: 12)
- Solicitation letters, 1976 (Folder 13: 13)
- South Carolina campaign, 1975 (Folder 13: 14)
- Specific, 1975 (Folder 13: 15)
- Speech - Draft file, undated (Folder 13: 16)
- Invitations, 1975-1976 (Folder 13: 17-18)
- Invitations, 1976 (Folder 13: 19)
- Invitations, pending, 1975-1976 (Folder 13: 20-21)
- Invitations, pending, 1975-1976 (Folder 14: 1-6)
- Invitations, regrets, 1975-1976 (Folder 14: 7-12)
- Invitations, regrets, 1976 (Folder 15: 1-8)
- Invitations, regrets, 1976 (Folder 16: 1)
- Speech regrets, 1975-1976 (Folder 16: 2-6)
- Speech regrets, 1975-1976 (Folder 17: 1-11)
- Speech regrets (by state or country), 1975-1976 (Folder 18)
  - Alabama (Folder 18: 1)
  - Alaska (Folder 18: 2)
  - Arizona (Folder 18: 3)
  - Arkansas (Folder 18: 4)
  - California (Folder 18: 5)
  - Colorado (Folder 18: 6)
  - Connecticut (Folder 18: 7)
  - Delaware (Folder 18: 8)
  - Florida (Folder 18: 9)
  - Georgia (Folder 18: 10)
  - Hawaii (Folder 18: 11)
  - Idaho (Folder 18: 12)
  - Illinois (Folder 18: 13)
  - Indiana (Folder 18: 14)
  - Iowa (Folder 18: 15)
  - Kansas (Folder 18: 16)
  - Kentucky (Folder 18: 17)
  - Louisiana (Folder 18: 18)
  - Maine (Folder 18: 19)
  - Maryland (Folder 18: 20)
  - Massachusetts (Folder 18: 21)
  - Michigan (Folder 18: 22)
  - Minnesota (Folder 18: 23)
  - Mississippi (Folder 18: 24)
  - Missouri (Folder 18: 25)
  - Montana (Folder 18: 26)
  - Nebraska (Folder 18: 27)
  - New Jersey (Folder 18: 28)
  - New Hampshire (Folder 18: 29)
  - New Mexico (Folder 18: 30)
  - New York (Folder 19: 1-3)
  - North Carolina (Folder 19: 4)
  - North Dakota (Folder 19: 5)
  - Ohio (Folder 19: 6)
  - Oklahoma (Folder 19: 7)
  - Oregon (Folder 19: 8)
  - Pennsylvania (Folder 19: 9)
  - South Carolina (Folder 19: 10)
  - South Dakota (Folder 19: 11)
  - Tennessee (Folder 19: 12)
  - Texas (Folder 19: 13)
  - Utah (Folder 19: 14)
  - Virginia (Folder 19: 15)
  - Washington (Folder 19: 16)
  - Washington, D.C. (Folder 19: 17)
  - West Virginia (Folder 19: 18)
  - Wisconsin (Folder 19: 19)
  - Wyoming (Folder 19: 20)
  - Canada (Folder 19: 21)
  - England (Folder 19: 22)
  - Mexico (Folder 19: 23)
- University speech requests (Folder 19: 24)
- Russo, Paul - Speech invitations (Folder 19: 25)
- Spending budget (inflation), 1975 (Folder 20: 1)
- Staff biographies, undated (Folder 20: 2)
- Staff meetings, 1976 (Folder 20: 3)
- Staff memoranda and procedures, 1976 (Folder 20: 4)
- State forms, 1975 (Folder 20: 5)
- State sub-division update - Citizens for Reagan state chairmen, treasurers, and banks, 1976 and undated (Folder 20: 6-8)
- Steffgen book - The Counterfeit Candidate, 1976 (Folder 20: 9)
- Student requests, 1975 (Folder 20: 10)
- Support (File # 3), 1975 (Folder 20: 11)
- Support letters (by month), 1975 (Folder 20)
  - July, 1975 (Folder 20: 12)
  - August, 1975 (Folder 20: 13)
  - September, 1975 (Folder 20: 14)
  - October, 1975 (Folder 20: 15)
  - November, 1975 (Folder 20: 16)
  - December, 1975 (Folder 20: 17)
- C and P Telephone company, undated (Folder 21: 1)
- Records of telephone calls. Includes "while you were out" message forms (Folder 21)
  - 1975 December 30 - 1976 February 9 (Folder 21: 2-8)
  - February 9-March 29, 1976 (Folder 22)
  - March 29-May 10, 1976 (Folder 23)
  - May 10-June 30, 1976 (Folder 24)
  - June 30-August 4, 1976 (Folder 25)
  - August 4-November 16, 1976 (Folder 26)
  - May 18-September 28, 1976 (Folder 26)
- Third party, 1975 (Folder 26: 1)
- Travel advance notes, 1976 (Folder 26)
  - January, 1976 (Folder 26: 2)
  - February, 1976 (Folder 26: 3)
  - March, 1976 (Folder 26: 4)
  - April, 1976 (Folder 26: 5)
  - May, 1976 (Folder 26: 6)
- Uzzell, Larry - Gerald Ford's electability, 1976 (Folder 27: 1)
- Vendors, general, 1975-1976 (Folder 27: 2)
- Vendors, Campaign materials, 1976 (Folder 27: 3)
- Ronald Reagan - Question of Vice Presidency, 1975 (Folder 27: 4)
- Volunteer thank you letters, 1976 (Folder 27: 5)
- Volunteers, statewide, 1975-1976 (Folder 27: 6)
- Washington office floor plan, undated (Folder 27: 7)
- Washington Post poll, 1975 December (Folder 27: 8)
- Young Americans for Freedom (YAP), 1975 (Folder 27: 9)
- ZIP run by state, undated (Folder 27: 10)
- Books by Gary Allen, 1976 (Folder 27)
- Sound recordings, circa 1976 (Folder 27)
  - Sound tape reels (Folder 27)
    - Indiana Citizens for Reagans (3 one-fourth inch sound reels) (Folder 27)
    - Michigan Citizens for Reagan (1 one-fourth inch sound reel) (Folder 27)
  - Frank Reynolds - American Broadcasting Corporation (ABC) television interview with John Sears, 1976 July 19 (Folder 27)
  - One-fourth inch sound reel (Folder 27)
  - 3 records 78 RPM (sent as promotional materials by Buddy Ring, Kit and Kay, and Kit Johnson) (Folder 27)
- Research materials - Jeff Bell, 1970-1976 (Box 28)
  - Agriculture and Services Agency, 1973 (Folder 28: 1)
  - Agriculture and food - California materials, 1973 (Folder 28: 2)
  - Business and transportation - California materials, 1973-1974 (Folder 28: 3)
  - Education - Position paper, 1976 (Folder 28: 4)
  - Energy development, 1976 (Folder 28: 5)
  - Department of Health - California materials, 1973-1974 (Folder 28: 6)
  - Human Resources Development - California materials, 1973-1974 (Folder 28: 7)
  - Ronald Reagan - Views on medicine, undated (Folder 28: 8)
  - Amended position papers - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Folder 28: 9)
  - Resources Agency - California materials (Folder 28: 10)
  - Speech excerpts, 1976 (Folder 28: 11)
  - Speech excerpts, 1976 (Folder 28: 1-3)
  - Summary of California accomplishments, 1974-1976 (Folder 28: 4)
  - Veterans Affairs and Community relations - California materials, 1970-1974 (Folder 28: 5)
- Southern states coordinator - David A. Keene, 1975-1976 (Folder 30)
  - Alabama, 1976 (Folder 30: 1)
  - Arkansas, 1975 (Folder 30: 2)
  - Delaware, undated (Folder 30: 3)
  - Florida, including report on Republicans in Florida, 1975-1976 (Folder 30: 4-6)
  - Georgia, 1976 (Folder 30: 7)
  - Indiana, 1975 (Folder 30: 8)
  - Kentucky, 1975-1976 (Folder 30: 9)
  - Louisiana, 1975-1976 (Folder 31: 1)
  - Maryland, 1975-1976 (Folder 31: 2)
  - Minnesota, 1975-1976 (Folder 31: 3)
  - Mississippi, 1975-1976 (Folder 31: 4)
  - New Jersey, undated (Folder 31: 5)
  - New York, includes poll, 1976, 1975-1976 (Folder 31: 6-7)
  - North Carolina, 1975-1976 (Folder 31: 8)
  - North Carolina, 1975 (Folder 31: 9-10)
  - South Carolina, 1975-1976 (Folder 31: 11)
  - Tennessee, 1975-1976 (Folder 31: 12)
  - Texas, including a photographic print of Robert Edwin Cook, 1975-1976 (Folder 31: 13)
  - Virginia, 1975-1976 (Folder 32: 1)
  - Wisconsin, 1975-1976 (Folder 32: 2)
  - Washington, undated (Folder 32: 3)
  - West Virginia, 1975-1976 (Folder 32: 4-6)
- Convention, 1975 (Folder 32: 7)
- Ed Nichols Associates, 1975 (Folder 32: 8)
- Press releases, 1976 (Folder 32: 9)
- Republican National Committee, 1976 (Folder 32: 10)
- Republican National Committee - Correspondence, 1976 (Folder 32: 11)
- Resumes, 1976 (Folder 32: 12)
- Schedule, 1976 and undated (Folder 32: 13)
- Southern list, undated (Folder 32: 14)
- List of staff at Citizens for Reagan national headquarters, Washington, D.C., undated (Folder 32: 15)
- Staff memoranda, 1976 (Folder 32: 16)
- Travel expense form, 1976 (Folder 32: 17)
- Truck rental information, undated (Folder 32: 18)
- Clippings, 1975-1976 (Folder 32)
  - undated (Folder 33: 1)
  - October, 1975 (Folder 33: 2)
  - January, 1976 (Folder 33: 3)
  - February, 1976 (Folder 33: 4)
  - March, 1976 (Folder 33: 5)
  - April, 1976 (Folder 33: 6)
  - May, 1976 (Folder 33: 7)
  - June, 1976 (Folder 33: 8)
  - July, 1976 (Folder 33: 9)
  - August, 1976 (Folder 33: 10)
  - Foreign press, 1976 (Folder 33: 11)
  - Unsorted, undated (Folder 34: 1-5)
  - Ronald Reagan, 1968-1976 (Folder 34)
    - Attacks, 1974-1976 (Folder 34: 6)
    - Statements, Newspapers, 1974-1976 (Folder 34: 7-8)
    - Statements, Standard, 1968-1976 (Folder 34: 9)
    - Support, 1973-1976 (Folder 34: 10)
- Policy statements, speeches, position papers, and press releases, 1974-1975 and undated (Folder 35)
  - Economy (Folder 35: 1)
  - Foreign affairs (Folder 35: 2)
  - Government (Folder 35: 3)
  - American spirit (Folder 36: 1)
  - Congress (Folder 36: 2)
  - Domestic affairs (Folder 36: 3)
  - Gerald Ford and Grand Old Party (GOP) (Folder 36: 4)
- Citizens for Reagan (CFR) research functions, undated (Folder 37: 1)
  - Master catalogue, undated (Folder 37: 2)
    - Position papers (Folder 37)
    - Adoption vs. abortion, undated (Folder 37: 3)
    - Abortion, 1976 (Folder 37: 4)
    - Abortion vs. refugees, undated (Folder 37: 5)
    - Agriculture, 1976 (Folder 37: 6)
    - Amnesty, 1976 (Folder 37: 7)
    - Big government, undated (Folder 37: 8)
    - Boondoggles, undated (Folder 37: 9)
    - Budget, undated (Folder 37: 10)
    - Bureaucracy, undated (Folder 37: 11)
    - Busing, undated (Folder 37: 12)
    - California records I and II, 1976 and undated (Folder 37: 13-14)
    - Capital punishment, undated (Folder 37: 15)
    - Capitalism, 1975 (Folder 37: 16)
    - Capitalism/Socialism, undated (Folder 37: 17)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), undated (Folder 37: 18)
    - China, 1976 (Folder 37: 19)
    - Communism, undated (Folder 37: 20)
    - Confidence in government, undated (Folder 37: 21)
    - Conservation, undated (Folder 37: 22)
    - Calvin Coolidge/Dwight D. Eisenhower, undated (Folder 37: 23)